Look at us! We're
like the Rockettes!
(Barry:)En garde,
Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Prepare yourself
for a rigorous touching.
(Spanish accent):
My name is Inigo Montoya.
(Howard:)You killed my father.
(Howard:)Prepare to die.
(Spanish accent):
My name
(Howard:)is Inigo Montoya.
You killed my
father. Prepare
(Howard:)to die.
(Howard:)I thought
you were Puss in Boots.
(Raj:)Oh, yeah, right. Sorry.
(Spanish accent):
My name is Puss in Boots.
(Howard:)You killed my father.
(Howard:)Prepare to die.
(Sheldon:)I'm looking forward to him
teaching us glove-slapping.
(Leonard:)What?
(Sheldon:)You know, when my
honor is insulted,
(Sheldon:)and I need to challenge
someone to a duel
(Sheldon:)by slapping them across
the face with my glove.
When was your honor insulted?
(Sheldon:)My last physical.
(Leonard:)Again, that doctor
didn't insult your honor.
(Leonard:)Just checked your prostate.